## Pitchayakit Pahamak Software Engineer

Last update: March 29, 2023

The online version is available at

https://pitchayakit.github.io/cv

#### Residence

Bangkok, Thailand

#### **Phone**

**\** +66831225471

#### **GitHub**

pitchayakit

#### **Email**

☑ pitchayakit.p@gmail.com

```
Laravel
       +++++
                       +++++ Livewire ++++
                                              AlpineJs
                                                      ++++
                                                              jQuery
                                                                      ++++
                                                                               SCSS +++++
                                                             GIT
Tailwind
       ++++
               Bootstrap ++++ WordPress ++++
                                               Restful
                                                      + + + +
                                                                      + + + +
                                                                              SQL ++++
 VueJs
      +++
              NodeJs
                              Linux +++
                                               Nginx
                                                      +++
                                                              Python
```

Over 6 years of software development career in a variety of companies including startup and digital agency. I graduated with a Master's degree in Network Learning Technology, NCU, Taiwan. I has been working on both back-end and front-end website development. Moreover, I am intersted in IoT and Machine learning. Please get in touch.

## **Professional Experience**

#### Lexicon

2020 - Present

- Maintenance web server and CI/CD flow
- Writing clean, testable, high quality code
- Managed up Line CRM system
- Managed up CMS using Laravel, Nova, and WordPress
- Elasticsearch
- Data migration
- Coaching junior developer in web development and technical support



#### Freelancer

2018 - 2020

- Managed up to 5 company websites
- Managed up to 2 E-commerce websites
- Managed up 1 library website for searching books using Laravel

WordPress | Laravel

## **Empag**

2017 - 2018

- · Coaching internships in web development and technical support
- Managed up to 4 web content management systems and tasks at a given time
- Collaborate with designer in order to ensure quality and accuracy of the designy
- A support tool for web scraping and export to excel file

WordPress NodeJs

## Onestockhome

Mar 2017 - Sep 2017

- Migration content management system to Ruby on Rail platform
- Developed front-end website using jQuery, Boostrap, HTML and CSS in Ruby on Rail platform
- Supported the use of content management system and improve user interface

Ruby on Rail React

## Rippleworkz

2016 - 2017

- Integrated HTML to WordPress and Prestashop
- Managed up to 4 webs content management system and tasks at a given time.
- Collaborate with project manager to develop website, which is beyond own management project

WordPress JQuery

# SeSaMe (Sensor-enhanced Social Media) Center, National University of Singapore

Jul 2015 - Dec 2015

- SENSE video analytics web application replaced video output for detection, tracking and counting by HTML Canvas
- Take over and developed SeSaMe website using Joomla CMS

Play Framework | HTML Canvas | Joomla | OpenCV | MongoDB

### **Education**

Master of Network Learning Technology, College of Electrical Engineering & Computer Science, National Central University, Taiwan [2018 - 2020]

Bachelor of Computer Engineering, College of Engineering, Kasetsart University, Thailand [2013 - 2016]

## **Additional Experience**

A Study of using IoT and Zenbo robot to facilitate students' interaction in flipped classroom and the analysis of their perception.

IoT Zenbo Machine learning

Smart home with door and light control System.

ToT PHP jQuery